# Rajab Bobomuratov



### **Junior Front-end Developer**

I'm a React Front-end developer with experience in UX/UI design and knowledge of the QA Manual.

I recently completed a course on JavaScript and React development, with a significant emphasis on self-study. There I got a base for working with JS, React, Redux/RTK, REST API, MUI, and more.

During my studies, I constantly tried to use additional technologies that were not included in the course plan.

I also worked and continue to work on the

- · UI library, which I used for personal tasks and as the main UI library in one of the final team tasks;
- · Npm library of TS scripts, where I put specific functions or functions that I use often;
- · Telegram bot for school chat, written on the Telegraf framework;
- · A set of API functions written in Google Apps Script a pseudo-backend for working with Google Spreadsheets via REST API.

In team tasks, I was a team leader, setting up projects, organizing processes, and communicating.

During the course, I held the status of 'rs-activist' for helping other students and moderating a Ukrainian-language chat on Telegram.

Throughout my studies, I started taking notes in Notion, which turned into a mini encyclopedia that is sometimes used by close classmates or people who know about it.

I also have non-commercial / semicommercial experience in developing

scripts and tools in JS (Figma, After Effects, Studio One), Lua (Reaper DAW), AHK (Windows OS) and some other languages. I love to experiment and am always in the process of learning something

new. Furthermore, I am not afraid to use new approaches and change my habits if I see logic and growth for myself.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Junior UX/UI Designer

APR 2021 - JUL 2021 // unqa.agency (agency, Rivne)

Web design, corporate identity and logo design

Presentation of projects to the customer

#### **Graphic Designer**

DEC 2011 - JAN 2015 // Bureau MarT (advertising consulting agency, Rivne)

Logos design, corporate styles, outdoor advertising, printed and souvenir products

### **EDUCATION**

### React

SEP 2022 - DEC 2022 // The Rolling Scopes School

React, Redux Toolkit, React API. 6 tasks, including a team task

### JavaScript/Front-end

MAR 2022 - SEP 2022 // The Rolling Scopes School

Core JavaScript, TypeScript, layout, algorithms, development under the supervision of a mentor. More than 7 projects, including a team task

I tried to use it myself: React, Redux (vanilla), Axios, Lottie animation, Web Animations API, etc. During the course, I created my own UI library and scripting library, which I used in all assignments

## JS/FE Pre-School

DEC 2021 - MAR 2022 // The Rolling Scopes School

Preparatory course for JavaScript/Front-end

During the course, we learned the basic basics of JS, HTML, CSS, and git. We tried to develop our own website, game, and work with RestAPI. Over than 5 personal projects

## **UX Design**

2021 // bangbangeducation

A video course on interface design

## **Basics of QA Manual**

AUG 2021 - AUG 2022 // QATestLab

A month-long course on the basics of QA manual testing

# **UX/UI** Design

2019 // WDIR A video course on web and interface design. Everything from working with a

client to the finished design

# **PROJECTS**

# AW O >

React, TypeScript, Redux, SCSS Modules, Vite, ESLint, Autoprefixer, Firebase, React Hook Form, Ameliance UI, ASM TS Scripts, React Responsive, React Router DOM, React Showfall, Google Apps Script

Pet Project

Single Page Application for use within a music group. The application contains a list of songs, chords, and a chat for communication. The app's

functionality includes the ability to create a song list and transpose chords The project was started at the beginning of my studies in vanilla JavaScript and later rewritten in React. Some of the functionality is in the process of

## More projects

being ported to React

on the web version of CV > on github →

#### Message me on Telegram

Location: Rivne, remote

Telegram: @amelianceskymusic

+380 (97) 123 57 33

E-mail: radzhab@ukr.net

**GitHub:** github.com LinkedIn: linkedin.com

### **HARD SKILLS**

React

TypeScript

**Phone:** 

JavaScript

Redux / RTK

HTML

CSS / SCSS / SCSS Modules

MUI

Webpack

Vite

Create React App

ESLint / Prettier

Git / GitHub

React Router Dom

React Hook Form

Rest API

#### **Others**

Visual Studio Code

Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator

Json, Yaml, Ini

Notion, Jira, Slack

Handwrite

### **SOFT SKILLS**

Adaptability

Critical thinking

Focus on results

Friendly

Perfectionism

Honesty

Self-development

Stress tolerance

# **LANGUAGES**

## **English**

A1

**Polish** 

A1

#### **Ukrainian** Native

# **HOBBIES**

I am musician. I play musical instruments and compose music

In my free time I like to write code, automate routine tasks, ride a bike